[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：让我们谈谈如何使用生成器来解决我们的运行示例
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Let's talk about how to use a generator to solve our running example of
并行文件尽快渲染。
parallel files ASAP rendering.
首先，这个get file函数当前是
First thing this get file function is currently
给你一个ASQ返回的能力。
given to you with an ASQ returning capability.
如果你回报一个承诺，同样的事情可能会发生。
Exactly the same thing could happen if you return a Promise.
所以你没有理由在这里做异步，序列。
So there's no reason you have to do asynquence, sequences, here.
因为我提供给你的跑步者能够理解承诺
Because the runner that I've provided you is capable of understanding Promises
和序列一样好。
equally well with sequences.
我刚开始在那里，因为那是我们去过的地方
I just started out there because that's the place that we were
在另一个练习结束时。
at the end of the other exercise.
但并不要求这只是一个序列。
But there is no requirement that this is a sequence only.
[咳嗽]好的，我们要做asq().runner。
[COUGH] Okay, so we're gonna do ASQ().runner.
记住我要把这个括号放在这里。
Remember I gotta put this parentheses on here.
你必须开始一个序列，因为这是一个序列的方法
You have to start a sequence cuz this is a method of a sequence rather
而不是静态函数。
than a static function.
我将通过它&gt；&gt；Kyle：一个发电机
And I'm gonna pass it &gt;&gt; Kyle: A generator which
我现在给梅恩打电话。
I'll call main for now.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：这是我的基本设置。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: That's my basic set up.
如果你在这节课结束后再也不用异步了，你就去了
If you ended up after this class never using asynquence again and you went and
你用了联合公用事业猜猜你要做什么。
you used the co utility guess what you're gonna do.
你要用co替换那个部件，如果你最终使用了q库
You gonna replace that part with co and if you ended up using the Q library
你要把那部分换成Q.spawn，好吗？
you're gonna replace that part with Q.spawn, okay?
所以他们每个人都有相同的效用。
So every one of them has the same utility on it.
我在这里教你的所有东西都不是异步特定的。
All the stuff that I'm teaching you here is not asynquence specific.
好的，现在我们的实用程序中，我们需要调用getFile函数并
All right, now inside of our utility, we need to call the getFile function and
当它回应我们时，我们需要把它打印出来。
when it responds to us then we need to print it out.
所以我们可以说，text1=收益率
So we could say, text1 = yield
getFile(“file1”)；以及
getFile("file1"); and
然后输出(Text1)；。
then output(text1);.
然后我们可以说text2=产量
And then we could say text2 = yield
getFile(“File2”)；和output(Text2)；。
getFile("file2"); and output(text2);.
然后text3=生成getFile(“file3”)；以及
And then text3 = yield getFile("file3"); and
输出(Text3)，以及
output(text3), and
然后输出(“完成！”)，好吗？
then output("Complete!"), okay?
我们可以这么做。
We could do that.
各位，在我们回答这是不是完全正确之前
Does everybody, before we answer whether or not this is fully correct or
正确的方式，每个人都看到它是如何工作的吗？
the right way, does everybody see how that would work?
我们要等
We're going to wait for
在此请求完成之前分配的text1。
text1 to get assigned until after this request finishes.
这就是YERENCE关键字在这里给我们的结果。
So that's what the yield keyword is giving us here.
我们在这个Ajax调用上让步。
We're yielding on this Ajax call.
这是一个承诺，所以我们放弃了跑步者的承诺
This is a Promise, so we're yielding out the Promise the runner in
Asynquence知道如何处理该序列的承诺
asynquence knows what to do with that Promise of that sequence and
它等待简历并把数据还给我们，好吗？
it waits resumes and gives us the data back, okay?
但现在，有人发现这个问题了吗？
But now, does anybody spot a problem with this?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：这不是一个请求，如果它-&gt；&gt；Kyle：完全正确，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's not a request if it- &gt;&gt; Kyle: Exactly,
你看，我们甚至在这个完成之前都不会叫这个
see we're not even calling this one until after this one finishes
有违反我们平行原则的权利。
have violates our in parallel principle right.
所以，如果你想在生成器中做顺序运算，这是相当容易的。
So, if you want to do sequentiality in generators, it's pretty easy.
你只需将一个函数调用放在一个产量之后，它将是连续的。
You just put a function call after a yield, and it's going to be sequential.
但是如果你想做并行的事情，你必须一直这样
But if you wanna do things in parallel, you have to be ever so
稍微聪明一点。
slightly more clever.
所以我们要这么做
So here's what we're gonna do.
我将接受getFile调用并将其移动到这里。
I'm going to take that getFile call and move it up here.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：我要接那个电话。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: And I'm gonna take that call.
我要把它移到这里。
And I'm going to move it here.
你会注意到，我没有在这些呼叫中放入YERENCE关键字，
And you'll notice that I'm not putting the yield keyword in those calls,
那是故意的。
that's on purpose.
所以现在，如果我同时要求他们三个人，
So now, if I requested all three of them in parallel,
大家都看到了吗，一整天都是一样的，好吗？
does everybody see that, exactly the same as it's been all day long, okay?
现在我已经收到了那些getFile调用，我不再需要那些了。
Well now that I've got those getFile calls, I don't need those anymore.
那我要用什么来代替他们呢？
So what am I gonna replace them with?
我会用承诺代替他们，好吗？
I'm gonna replace them with the Promise, all right?
&gt；&gt；kyle：所以现在我们要求平行排序他们的输出。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So now we have request in parallel sequencing their output.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：每个人都看到我是怎么做到的吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Does everybody see how I did that?
因为承诺，他们做什么？
Cuz the promises, what do they do?
他们最基本的事情是什么，甚至是敲击，他们做什么？
What is their most fundamental thing, even thumps, what do they do?
它们消除了时间状态。
They eliminate the time state.
所以这些什么时候能相对完成并不重要，
So it doesn't matter when when these are going to relatively finish,
我们将根据我们编写产量代码的方式对他们的响应进行排序。
we're going to sequence their responses based upon how we write the yield code.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：不是将产量p1分配给文本1，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Instead of assigning the yield p1 to text1,
你能不能说输出-&gt；&gt；Kyle：我马上就到了。
could you just say output- &gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm about to get there.
我只是想确保每个人都明白这部分，好吗？
I'm just asking to make sure everybody understands this part, okay?
有没有人理解这部分有困难？
Is there anybody that having trouble understanding this part?
好的，现在就像你刚才说的，我把这个赋值给一个变量，然后
All right, so now exactly as you just said, I'm assigning this to a variable and
然后立即打印变量。
then immediately printing the variable.
为什么我需要变量。
Why do I need the variable.
为什么不直接把这个收益率p1放在那里，把那条线去掉。
Why not just take this yield p1 and put it right there and take that line out.
把这个产额p2放在那里，去掉那些线。
And take this yield p2 and put it right there and take those lines out.
然后取这个产额p3，把它放在那里，去掉那些线。
And take this yield p3 and put it right there and take those lines out.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：多酷啊？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: How cool is that?
将其与我们从起点开始逐步构建的内容进行比较
Compare that to what we've progressively been building from where we started
这个研讨会的开始就是那些荒谬的回电噩梦。
the beginning of this workshop with all that ridiculous callback nightmare.
然后在承诺，在映射和减少，在不同步中砰的一声。
Then thunks in Promises, in map and reduce, in asynquence.
我们变得越来越好。
We got better and better and better.
但是你们中有多少人觉得我们已经达到了很大程度上
But how many of you feel like we've arrived at something a whole lot
比我们开始的地方好，对吧？
better than where we started, right?
没有任何新功能。
No new functionality whatsoever.
只是一个完全不同的
Just an entirely different and
表达相同代码的更好方式，这有什么关系呢？
better way of expressing the same code, why does that matter?
因为我们的代码是一种交流形式。
Because our code is a form of communication.
我们不仅需要与其他团队成员沟通，还需要
We need to communicate not only with our other team members but
关于代码应该做什么的未来的自我。
with our future selves of what the code supposed to do.
这更有表现力。
This is more expressive.
它更容易理解，更易读，更容易学习。
It's more understandable, it's more readable, it's more learnable.
考虑到像这样编写代码的能力，我不能理解我是如何使用它的
Given the ability to write code like that I cannot understand how I spent so
很多年都在写其他的废话。
many years writing all that other crap.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我希望我可以回去
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I wish I could go back and
修复我编写的所有其他不好的代码片段。
fix all those other bad pieces of code that I wrote.
关于练习七有问题吗？
Any questions about exercise seven?
这里没有其他魔法。
There's no other magic here.
我要挑战你回去
I'm going to challenge you to go back and
重新阅读幻灯片，并重试练习。
reread through the slides, and retry the exercises.
但它真的就像它看起来那样简单。
But it really is as simple as it looks right there.
这真的很简单，就像问我自己，我需要一些并行发生的事情吗？
It really is as simple as asking myself, do I need something to happen in parallel?
如果是这样的话，将这些东西存储到中间承诺中，然后
If so, store those things into intermediate Promises and
然后对他们的反应进行排序。
then sequence their responses.
我需要让它们按顺序发生吗？
Do I need to have them happen sequentially?
确保他们出现在产量关键字之后，就是这样。
Make sure they show up after yield keywords, that's it.
如果你需要更高层次的抽象
And if you need higher levels of abstraction like some
我们和Promises谈过的那些抽象概念，在所有或其他类似的事情上。
of those abstractions we talked about with Promise.at all or other things like that.
猜猜你有什么机会得到所有的东西这些只是承诺。
Guess what you have access to all that stuff these are just Promises.
因此，您可以在以下任一选项中使用promis.all和promis.raise
So you can use promise.all and promise.raise in any of
这些其他抽象是必要的，因为它们都只是产生承诺。
those other abstractions as necessary because they all just produce promises.
所以你可以做一个承诺。所有的。
So you could do a yield promised.all.
如果您需要在进行下一步之前等待所有三个步骤都完成，
If you needed to wait on all three to finish before moving on to the next step,
只要放弃承诺就行了。
just yield promised.all.
如果你只需要听一个或三个来完成
If you need to only listen for one or three to finish and
你不关心哪个先发生，答应。提高。
you don't care which one happens first, yield promised.raise.
或者其他几十个抽象概念中的任何一个。
Or any of the other dozens of abstractions that are out there.
这是将承诺编入生成器模式的另一个好处，
That's another benefit of weaving Promises into the generator patterns,
如果我们需要的话，我们可以进入所有的障碍物。
that we have access to all those obstructions if we need it.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：异步编程中的任何复杂级别
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Any level of complexity that you have in asynchronous programming
可以编织成款式。
can be woven into the style.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：但是除非你练习，否则你不会到达那里，所以
&gt;&gt; Kyle: But you're not going to get there unless you practice this, so
我要挑战你不要让这是你最后一次看到它，
I'm going to challenge you don't let this be the last time you look at it,
你走开，你喜欢，这很酷，但我仍然会做所有的旧东西。
you walk away and you like, that's cool but I'm still gonna do all the old stuff.
是时候升级我们的游戏了。
It's time to up our game.
是时候练习了，试着让我们的大脑围绕着这种新的风格。
It's time to practice and try to get our brains wrap around this new style.
我向你保证，你的团队成员和你未来的自我
I promise you, your team members and your future self are gonna
感谢您在使代码更合理方面付出的更多努力。
thank you the more effort you put in making your code more reasonable.
好的，还有关于发电机和承诺的问题吗。
Okay, any more questions about generators and Promises.
我们感觉如何
How are we feeling so
感觉你的大脑开始有点糊涂了。
far feeling like your brains are starting get a little bit mush.
好的，两个方向都能看到一些。
Okay, see a few in both directions.
是的，你可能需要更多的咖啡因，这很酷，明白了。
Yeah you might need a little bit more caffeine that's cool, got it.
我们要休息一下。
We're gonna take a break.
所以，去给你自己的咖啡因，你的怪物饮料或其他什么东西充电吧。
So go get yourself a recharge of your caffeine your monster drink or whatever.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]&gt；&gt；Kyle：因为当我们回来的时候
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Kyle: Because when we come back
我们要吃红色的药丸，再往下走更远的兔子洞。
we're going to take the red pill and go even further down the rabbit hole.